Mrs. Maria, I want to ask, what are the things
that need to be considered as an
FPD insurance customer? As a customer, there are five
things that must be considered. First,
when receiving the policy book, read the
personal data information, product benefits, and the
policy premium due date. Second,
always update your personal data
such as your full name, email, telephone number,
and home address whenever there are changes.
Third, for customers who have
insurance policies that are linked to investments,
when making transactions such as
transferring funds or switching, make sure the
nominal investment value is sufficient so that
monthly fee payments run smoothly.
Fourth, if customers need to
upgrade or downgrade insurance benefits, it is
better not to close the old policy and
open a new policy because customers need to
wait again to be able to submit a
claim according to the applicable policy provisions.
Therefore, check the
latest policy regularly.
Always be careful in making
various transactions or receiving
information. Always be alert to
fraudulent actions in the name of FWD
insurance in
any form. Visit the website
fwd.co.id to find out the
official information on FWD insurance that is currently
in effect or contact FWD insurance customer care
at
15525. Thank you for the information, Mrs.
Maria
[Music] You're welcome